curricunet.com 2013-12-23

# Privacy | Governet

**We Protect Your Privacy**  
Governet is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We provide certain services and opportunities for visitors to our Web site. In order to provide these services to you and to develop a better site, we require that you submit some of your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

**Information Gathered**  
When you register to receive materials or complete an information form, Governet is collecting information from you. This information is necessary in order to tailor our subsequent communications to you, fulfill your requests regarding products and services, and to contact you about Governet developments.

**Information Sharing**  
Governet will not sell, rent, or share your personally identifiable information with others, unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may share aggregate data with our business partners, but this data is based on demographics and does not include any personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you’ve visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Governet may use cookies to identify what pages are being used and which ones aren’t. This helps us analyze the Web page traffic and improve our site. Governet may allow other companies that are present on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Other companies do not have access to Governet’s cookies. Governet wants to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than the data you chose to share with us. If you are uncomfortable with cookie technology, you may adjust your Web browser accordingly.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Governet may amend this policy occasionally. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you.

**Feedback**  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our use of personal information on this site, please [contact us](http://governet.net/contact "Contact Us") here.
